https://www.zippo.com/pages/cookie-policy

Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
Menu
Customize it!
0
Customize It!
Contact Information
Outside U.S.A.
USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES
This website is operated by Zippo Manufacturing Company, 33 Barbour Street Bradford, PA 16701, USA.  ZIPPO receives and records information from your browser when you use any ZIPPO site and may use a variety of methods, such as “Cookies” and “Pixel Tags” to collect this information.
A Cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on our website and allow us to enhance and personalize your online experience. For example, we use Cookies to:
Remember the items in your shopping cart
Recognize you when you return to our website
Store your username or login email and password to make it easier to login
Confirm that users are logged in
Enable you to use Express Checkout
Analyze visitor behavior
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a Cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all Cookies. If you turn all Cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your website experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place product orders over the telephone by contacting Consumer Relations number at 1-888-GGB-1932 (888-442-1932).
To change your web browser settings for cookies, follow the instructions in the help section of your web browser (or please visit allaboutcookies.org).
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to analyze your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website (including your IP address) is transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the United States of America. Google uses this information to assess your use of the website, providing reports on website activity for website operators and other website activity and internet related services. Google may transfer this information to third parties, if required by law or if third parties process the information on behalf of Google. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
View an overview of privacy at Google at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
USE OF ACUITY ADS
This website uses pixels and/or cookies placed by AcuityAds in order to help us deliver, measure, target and report on advertising campaigns on this website and other websites. The pseudonymous data collected via these pixels and cookies does not allow us or AcuityAds to identify you directly, but they allow them to recognize a user’s browser or device over time.  AcuityAds collects web log information such as a web visitor’s IP address, web pages viewed, date and time, domain type, and user interactions with advertisement delivered by AcuityAds or one of their third-party partners. AcuityAds retains the web log data collected via its pixels and cookies for up to three months, although we generally don’t retain this data for EU data subjects for more than a few days. Users can learn more about AcuityAds and may opt-out of certain uses of information by AcuityAds by visiting their privacy policy at https://www.acuityads.com/privacy-policy/.
USE OF AMAZON CONVERSION AND AMAZON REMARKETING PIXEL
This website uses the
Amazon Conversion Pixel and Amazon Remarketing Pixel services run by Amazon.com, Inc., 410 Terry Ave. North Seattle, WA, USA. For this purpose, Amazon has placed and uses Conversion and Remarketing Pixels on this website which, based on your prior consent, collect the IP address of the devices using this website, the type of browser being used and the type of device.
Amazon who is responsible for the data collection states that it only uses the full IP address for robot and fraud detection and otherwise truncates the last octet of the IP address. Amazon uses the pixels placed on your device to recognize your device, learn about what ads you see, what ads you click and other actions you take on this website and other sites and stores this information on its servers for nine months from the last action recorded for a specific user/device, so that it can provide more useful and relevant ads to you and to measure the success of advertising campaigns analyze the effectiveness of ads for statistical and market research purposes.
If you are visiting the website out of the EU/ European Economic Area (EEA), please note that your personal data may thus be transferred outside the EU/EEA to Amazon in the U.S.A., which does not provide the same level of protection of personal data as in the EU/EEA.
Amazon states that it does not provide any personal data to advertisers or third party sites, except for the IP address. However, advertisers and other third parties may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized ad or content are part of the group that the ad or content is directed towards. Also, some third parties may provide Amazon with information about you from offline or online sources which Amazon may link to your user profile. For more information on how Amazon (and its affiliates) uses pixels and interest based ads see here. Zippo, on the other hand, do not collect any data through those pixels and do not receive any personal data from Amazon.
Refusal or withdrawal of consent to the pixels has no adverse consequences for your use of the website. If you provided consent to the use of those pixels when accessing this website, you can withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal, by clicking here. For information about your other rights, please click here.
You can prevent recording of the data generated by the Amazon pixels by clicking on the following link and checking the setting for “Do not personalize advertising displayed by Amazon for this Internet browser”: https://www.amazon.com/adprefs. Alternatively, you can check the corresponding settings at http://www.youronlinechoices.com. By doing so, an opt-out cookie is set in your browser which prevents the future recording of your data by Amazon when visiting this website.
USE OF CENTRO PIXEL
This website uses the Centro cookie for the purpose of providing consumers with personalized advertising.  The cookie is set by Centro, Inc. via the *.sitescout.com domain.  The data collected through the cookie, including a unique user ID, is processed by Centro, Inc. and may be disclosed to third parties for the purpose of user matching. Centro states it deletes the user IDs after 30 days of inactivity. Centro includes the AdChoices icon on all behaviorally targeted ads to allow the user to opt-out.  Users can also opt-out at https://www.centro.net/privacy-policy/.
USE OF EMX COOKIES/PIXEL
This website uses the EMX pixels/cookies, which collect data to understand the interests and characteristics of users and to optimize online video ads.  EMX states it collects data such as segment data, browser type, IP address, domain names, operating systems, language preferences, platform type, device location, access dates and times, referring website addresses, browsing and search activity, online transactions, randomly-generated unique cookie ID numbers relating to  specific user, and in some cases, estimated age range and gender.  EMX states that it does not collect personally-identifiable information as defined by the Network Advertising Alliance and Digital Advertising Alliance, although some may be considered pseudonymized data in the European Union.  Users can control the collection and use of such data by adjusting their device setting or opting out with the Network Advertising Initiative or Digital Advertising Alliance at either https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices or https://www.aboutads.info/choices. EMX states that it does not retain data for longer than 24 months. EMX’s privacy policy is located at https://emxdigital.com/privacy/.
USE OF FACEBOOK PIXEL
This website uses the Facebook pixel, a small piece of JavaScript code, that is added to the website in order to optimize ads, report on the success of advertising campaigns across devices and target ads to the audience. The Facebook pixel sends information about your browsing session through HTTP headers to Facebook, including the IP address, information about the web browser, page location, document, referrer and web browser user agent. Pixel-specific data includes pixel ID and Facebook cookie data to connect the events to a specific Facebook ad account and to make a match to a person known by Facebook. Facebook checks whether the person has previously seen or interacted with an ad from our account or if the person matches an audience rule and prepares an analytics report, which contains anonymized or aggregated data. Facebook keeps the information collected from the pixels for 180 days and stores the data collected in its production data centers in the US and in Sweden. Facebook supports the DAA’s AdChoices to opt out of behavioral advertising and you can check the corresponding settings at http://optout.aboutads.info to opt out from the Facebook pixel. You can also learn more about why you are seeing an ad through Facebook’s AdsPreferences (available here: https://www.facebook.com/help/109378269482053/?helpref=hc_fnav).
USE OF MAGNETIC COOKIES/PIXEL
This website uses the Magnetic pixel/cookies, which enables the delivery of in-store product recommendations, personalized email marketing services, audience and customer analytics, and personalized advertisements, and to analyze the effectiveness of these services.  Magnetic Media Inc. states that it collects data such as information about users’ browsers or devices, IP address, date and time of visit, search data, webpage information, and data segments.  Magnetic states that it may share such data with Zippo and its partners for purposes such as sending targeted ads and improving offerings and services. Magnetic states it retains most of the data for 24 months. To opt out of receiving personalized ads from Magnetic, please visit http://www.magnetic.com/about/opt-out/. To opt out of receiving personalized ads from Magnetic and other advertising companies, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/. Other consumer choice tools are provided through the Ghostery Enterprise opt-out program (available at http://choices.ghosteryenterprise.com/global-opt-out.html). The Magnetic privacy notice is available at https://www.magnetic.com/policy-page/#privacy.
USE OF MiQ PIXEL
MiQ uses the Universal Pixel and Conversion Pixel to inform bidding / targeting strategies, provide user level insights, and drive stronger campaign performance. MiQ states that it collects the following data: cookie ID, referrer URL, & timestamp.  MiQ states that it does not disclose the data to third parties/ MiQ states that it retains the data for 6 months.  MiQ’s privacy policy & users opt-out methodology is available at https://www.wearemiq.com/privacy-policy .
USE OF PINTEREST PIXEL
This website uses the Pinterest tag, which helps optimize ads on Pinterest, report on the success of Promoted Pins, and create audiences to target on Promoted Pins.  Pinterest collects the following data: insights about actions that a person takes on the website after viewing an ad on Pinterest.  Pinterest does disclose data to third parties to help analyze and improve their services, market Pinterest to users on other sites and apps, or to comply with laws, regulations, or legal requests. Pinterest retains the data only so long as it needs it to provide Pinterest to you and fulfill the purposes described in the Privacy Policy.  That is also the case for anyone Pinterest shares your information with and who carries out services on their behalf.  Pinterest will remove your data from their systems or depersonalize it so it can't be identified once it no longer needs your information.  Users can opt-out through their Pinterest personalization settings (https://www.pinterest.com/settings/) or the AdChoices website (optout.aboutads.info). Pinterest’s privacy policy is available at https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy
USE OF REDDIT PIXEL
This website uses the Reddit Pixel, which helps optimize ads on Reddit and report on the success of Reddit ads. Reddit states that it collects the following data: measurements of actions taken on the website after interacting with an ad on Reddit.  Reddit states that it does disclose the data to third parties under the following conditions: with linked services; with Reddit partners; to comply with the law; in an emergency; to enforce Reddit policies and rights; with Reddit affiliates; with user consent; aggregated or de-identified information. Reddit states that it stores the information it collects for as long as it is necessary for the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected. Reddit also states it may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law. Users can opt-out through their Reddit personalization preferences (https://www.reddit.com/personalization) or the AdChoices website (https://optout.aboutads.info/). Reddit’s privacy policy is available at https://www.redditinc.com/policies/privacy-policy.
USE OF SIMPLI.FI PIXELS
This website uses retargeting and conversion pixels, which allows Simpli.fi to provide targeted advertising to users visiting the site and to report on the success of advertising campaigns. Simpli.fi states that it collects the following data where available: Precise geo-location, Device ID, IP address and performance data associated with these audiences (impressions, clicks and conversions). Simpli.fi does not disclose any personal information to third parties. Simpli.fi states that it retains the cookie-level data for 30 days. Users can opt-out here: https://optout.simpli.fi/opt-out. Simpli.fi’s privacy policy is available at https://simpli.fi/site-privacy-policy/
USE OF TWITTER WEBSITE TAG
This website uses the Twitter website tag, which helps optimize Twitter ads and report on the success of Twitter ads. Twitter collects the following data: insights about actions that a person takes on the website after viewing an ad on Twitter. Twitter states that it does disclose the data to third parties in the following instances: upon user consent; with service providers that help operate Twitter services; in compliance with law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; to protect the safety of any person; to protect the safety or integrity of the platform; to address fraud, security, or technical issues; to protect Twitter’s rights or property or the rights or property of those who use Twitter services; and with Twitter affiliates. Twitter states that it retains Log Data for a maximum of 18 months.  Users can opt-out through their Twitter Privacy and Safety Settings (https://twitter.com/settings/safety) or the AdChoices website (https://optout.aboutads.info). Twitter’s privacy policy is available at https://twitter.com/en/privacy
CALIFORNIA DO-NOT-TRACK DISCLOSURES
Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track signal, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. For information about Do Not Track, visit www.allaboutdnt.org. Zippo does not track its customers over time and across third party websites and, at this time, does not respond to Do Not Track browser settings or signals. Further, Zippo has not authorized third parties to collect personally identifiable information about users’ online activities over time and across different websites when users visit the Zippo website.
PRIVACY POLICY
View our full Privacy Policy (both for U.S.A. and outside U.S.A.).
Customize it!
Support
Contact Us
About Us
Accessibility
Careers
My Account
Store Locator
Customize it!
© 2020 - Zippo Manufacturing Company - All rights reserved
Terms & Conditions
Privacy & Legal
CCPA
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
By continuing on this website you consent to our use of cookies and similar technology, which collect and share with third parties the IP address of your device and browsing information, to make your browsing experience as useful as possible. For more information, see our Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy.
Close
